https://foodforlanecounty.org/privacy-policy/

our community to create
access to food.
Privacy Policy
FOOD for Lane County (FFLC) respects the privacy of our donors, and prospective donors.  All personal information from or concerning those people is kept strictly confidential by paid staff and volunteers unless the donors or prospective donors grant permission to use the information.  Personal information includes names and addresses, nature and value of prospective or past gifts, employers, business addresses, credit card numbers, social security numbers, email addresses, etc.  All electronic data is stored on a secure server with restricted access.  FFLC uses industry standard encryption and security protocols when processing and storing personal information.  Online donations are processed by Authorize.net, the industry leader in secure financial transactions.
FFLC does not sell, rent, or transmit personal information to other organizations unless we have formed a partnership to enhance services we offer and we have received prior assurances that the organization will comply with FFLC’s privacy policy.
FFLC may use personal information, with permission, for referral, testimonial, or example.  Information may also be used to conduct business transactions such as processing online donations, responding to information requests, and customizing fundraising procedures.
FFLC does not collect any personal information via its website.  Unless a person calls, faxes, or emails FFLC and identifies himself or herself, FFLC is unaware of the person’s identity. FFLC may, however, collect standard aggregate data such as pages visited and files downloaded, in order to improve the functionality of the website and to report to grantors.  Such information is not linked to individual donors.
Donors, prospective donors, and others may receive correspondence from FFLC after submitting a donation or other communication through FFLC’s website.  Such persons may opt out of future communications by contacting us.
The privacy of donors, prospective donors, website visitors, and members of the general public is important to FFLC.  To update personal information or ask questions about FFLC’s privacy statement, contact us.
Share This Page
Latest News
Thank you for supporting Holiday Farm Fire relief centers
COVID-19 VIDEO UPDATE: Grocery Store Recovery
COVID-19 VIDEO UPDATE: Summer Food Program
Upcoming Events
Thu
10
